Guide to the Eva J. Salber Papers, 1937-1990
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Eva J. Salber papers 1937-1990
Salber, Eva J., 1916-1990
17.1 linear feet Extent: circa 12,930 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.01130
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Portions of this collection are restricted.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The papers of Eva J. Salber (1937-1990) were donated to the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library from 1989-1991 by Eva J. Salber and Harry T. Phillips.
Biographical Note
1916, Jan. 5 Born, Capetown, South Africa
1938 M.B., Ch.B., University of Capetown
1939, Nov. 1 Married Harry T. Phillips
1956 Moved to United States (naturalized in 1961)
1957-1958 Milton Research Associate in Maternal and Child Health, Harvard School of Public Health, Boston, Mass.; Fellow in Medicine, Children's Hospital Medical Center, Boston, Mass.
1958-1967 Assistant Physician in Medicine, Children's Hospital Medical Center, Boston, Mass.
1961-1967 Senior Research Associate in Epidemiology, Harvarpd School of Public Health
1966-1967 Scholar, Radcliffe Institute for Independent Study
1967-1969 Director, Martha M. Eliot Family Health Center, Boston, Mass. Associate in Medicine, Children's Hospital Medical Center, Boston, Mass.
1967-1970 Lecturer in Pediatrics, Harvard Center for Community Health and Medical Care, Boston, Mass.
1969-1970 Senior Research Associate, Harvard Center for Community Health and Medical Care
1971-1973 Fellow, Royal Society of Health
1972 Lecturer, School of Public Health, University of North Carolina Director, Community Health Models, Duke University Medical Center
1972-1982 Professor, Department of Community Health Sciences, Duke University Medical Center
1975 Research Associate, Health Services Research Center, University of North Carolina
1980 Senior International Fellow, Fogarty International Center, National Institute of Health
1982- Professor Emeritus, Duke University
1990, Nov. 11 Died
Published books include: Caring and Curing: Community Participation in Health Services (1975); Community Health Education: The Lay Advisor Approach (1977); Services to the Elderly in England (1980); Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead: Voices of Rural Elderly (1983) and The Mind is Not the Heart: Recollections of a Woman Physician (1989). Salber conducted research in the areas of epidemiology (especially smoking in schoolchildren and breast cancer) and the utilization of medical care services.
Collection Overview
The Salber Papers span the years 1937 to 1990, with the bulk of the papers dating from 1967 to 1990. The collection contains correspondence; financial papers; writings and speeches; clippings; photographs, many by Dominic D'Eustachio; reports; minutes; scrapbooks; training manuals; student papers; printed material; and lecture notes chiefly relating to Salber's publications, teaching career, and work as a community health physician. Publications highlighted include
Caring and Curing (New York, N.Y., 1975)
Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead (Durham, N.C., 1983)
, containing interviews with the rural elderly in Durham County, N.C.; and
The Mind is Not the Heart (Durham, N.C., 1989). Her work in the community health field is documented primarily in her writings, the papers about the Martha M. Eliot Family Health Center, and the Health Facilitator Program, which was administered through the Duke University Medical Center Department of Community and Family Medicine. Outgrowths of the Health Facilitator Program are featured in the information about the Health and Human Services Program of the General Baptist State Convention of North Carolina. Other topics include smoking research among young people, teacher and student relationships, and the financing of community health service projects. The collection contains few personal papers and little information about Salber prior to 1967. Explanatory notes by Salber scattered throughout the collection offer insights rarely available in manuscript collections.
Salber's work as a community health physician is reflected primarily in the Writings and Speeches Series, Martha M. Eliot Family Health Center Series, and Duke University Medical Center Series. The Health Facilitator Program represented in the Duke University Medical Center Series is well described. One of its unique features was to identify lay persons within a community to aid health professionals in their work. Serving as a paradigm for other programs, there is data about some of them in the Health Facilitator Program Outgrowths Series.
The collection contains extensive information about Salber's work Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead, including interviews on audiocassettes, typed transcripts of many interviews, photographs of some of the persons interviewed, as well as correspondence and reviews pertaining to the book's publication. Information regarding this publication as well as others are found in the Writings and Speeches Series. Information relating to Salber's teaching is found chiefly in the Teaching Files Series and the Student Files Series. Papers concerning smoking research are found in the Project Files Series, while those respecting the financing of community health service projects are found in the Financial Papers: Funding Series.
Subject Headings
Salber, Eva J.; D'Eustachio, Dominic; Baptist State Convention of North Carolina. Health and Human Services Program; Martha M. Eliot Family Health Center (Boston, Mass.); Duke University. Dept. of Community and Family Medicine. Health Facilitator Program; Community health services; Aged -- North Carolina -- Durham County -- Interviews; Durham County (N.C.) -- Rural conditions; Women physicians -- United States; Smoking -- In adolescence; Teacher-student relationships; Community health services -- Finance; Aged -- North Carolina -- Durham County -- Photographs; Poor -- Medical care -- Massachusetts -- Boston; Photographs; Rural population -- North Carolina -- Personal narratives
Contents of Collection
- Correspondence, 1937-1990, undated(bulk 1970-1990).
  Letters, chiefly typed, both personal and professional, a few cards and printed items. Includes copies of Salber's outgoing correspondence. Explanatory notes added later by Salber are attached to some letters.
  Arranged chronologically.
  - 1957-1990, undated, (3 folders) (Box 1)
- Financial Papers: Funding, 1972-1990, undated
  Correspondence, copies of funding proposals and application forms, summaries of research, reports to funding agencies, and financial information in the form of statements, budgets and receipts. A small amount of printed material. Explanatory notes added later by Salber are attached to some items.
  Arranged alphabetically by name of organization in General subseries. Arranged alphabetically by name of project in the Proposals subseries.
  - General
    - Administration on Aging, 1978-1980 (Box 1)
    - Biddle Foundation; Trent Foundation, 1985-1990 (Box 1)
    - Clark Foundation, 1976 (Box 1)
    - Clark Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 2)
    - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Robert W. Johnson Foundation, 1972-1977 (Box 2)
    - Lyndhurst Foundation, 1979-1990 (Box 2)
    - Mott Foundation, 1976-1982 (Box 2)
    - Z. Smith Reynolds Foundation, 1981-1988, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Possible sources, 1977-1982 (Box 2)
  - Proposals
    - Alternatives to Institutionalization of Elderly, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
    - Course: The Community as a Laboratory for Medical Students, 1977-1990 (Box 3)
    - Health Facilitator Program, 1974-1979 (Box 3)
    - Lay Advisor Approach, 1978-1979 (Box 3)
    - Research on Rural Elderly, 1978-1978 (Box 3)
    - Research Project in Primary Care, undated (Box 3)
- Writings and Speeches, 1951-1990, undated
  Chiefly material relating to Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead, Caring and Curing, and The Mind is Not the Heart, including typed manuscript drafts, black and white photographs, interviews recorded on audiocassette, typed transcripts of interviews; and to a lesser extent, copies of published volumes, interview summaries written by Salber, correspondence, handwritten notes, agreements signed by interviewees, film negatives, contact sheets, slides, a videocassette, charts, and clippings. Magnetic data cards are filed with some interviews. Other sections of the series include copies of published and unpublished articles written or co-written by Salber, texts of speeches given by Salber, drafts of papers, lecture notes, a bound copy of Salber's M.D. thesis, reports, photocopied articles, and transcripts of interviews with Salber. Explanatory notes added later by Salber can be found throughout the series.
  Arranged chronologically, then alphabetically by title or subject. For Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead, files containing interview transcripts, audiocassettes of interviews, and photographs used to illustrate the book (some of which are mounted), are arranged alphabetically within each of these categories according to the names of individuals interviewed. A cross-reference list for audiocassettes containing interviews with more than one person is located in the container list. Oversize photographs are housed in flat boxes with the collection.
  Material relating to Caring and Curing and Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead is restricted.
  - 1951-1973, (5 folders) (Box 3)
  - 1974-1986, (6 folders) (Box 4)
  - 1987-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Access is not Enough, 1979 (Box 5)
  - Caring and Curing:
    - Correspondence, 1970-1984, (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Draft of book, undated, (3 folders) (Box 5)
  - Caring and Curing: (Box 6)
    - Volume,1975 (Box 6)
    - Twenty One Stories Plus One (volume), undated(original title of Caring and Curing) (Box 6)
    - Interviews, 1969-1989, undated, (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Caring and Curing: (Box 7)
    - Interviews, 1969-1989, undated, (5 folders) (Box 7)
    - Miscellaneous, 1970-1987, undated (Box 7)
  - The Community as Patient--Who Gets Care? undated (Box 7)
  - Community Perspectives on Health Needs in Developing Countries (lecture), 1983-1984 (Box 7)
  - Community Support: Hospital Community Liaison, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead: (Box 8)
    - Correspondence,1982 (Box 8)
    - Draft, undated, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - Evaluations based on 10 interviews and early version of work,1981 (Box 8)
    - Interview summaries, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
    - Interviewees; Miscellaneous, 1978-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Interviewees:
      - Ball, Annie, 1975-1981, undated (Box 8)
      - Ball, Polly, 1976-1981, undated (Box 8)
      - Blalock, Lizzie, 1975-1980 (Box 9)
      - Blalock, Sallie M., 1976-1980 (Box 9)
      - Briggs, Nannie Mae, 1976-1980, undated (Box 9)
      - Bullock, Jonah, 1976-1980, undated (Box 9)
      - Chambers, Walter H., 1976-1979, undated (Box 9)
      - Chambers, Wilcie, 1976-1980, undated (Box 9)
      - Clayton, Ethel M., 1975-1981, undated (Box 9)
      - Clayton, Vera Elma B., 1975-1976, undated (Box 9)
      - Crabtree, Ernest, 1976-1980, undated (Box 9)
      - Daniel, Mabel, undated (Box 9)
      - Ellis, Vesta, 1980 (Box 9)
      - Farlow, Ora, 1975, undated (Box 9)
      - Garrett, James Maynard, 1976-1980, undated (Box 9)
      - Harris, Betty Lee, 1975-1981, undated (Box 10)
      - Harris, Myrtle, 1975-1980, undated (Box 10)
      - Hill, Betty, 1975-1981, undated (Box 10)
      - Ivy, Eva, undated (Box 10)
      - Jeffries, Lattie G., 1975-1981, undated (Box 10)
      - Jordan, Hattie Riley, 1976-1981, undated (Box 10)
      - Lipscomb, Earlie Nathan, 1976-1979, undated (Box 10)
      - Littrell, Julie, 1975-1980, undated (Box 10)
      - Lunsford, Elsie Rogers, 1975-1980, undated (Box 10)
      - Lyons, Maynard, 1975-1977, undated (Box 10)
      - McBride, Julie, 1975-1980, undated (Box 10)
      - McCrea, Viola, 1976-1980, undated (Box 10)
      - Mangum, Ella Lyons, 1975-1981, undated (Box 11)
      - Moore, Quinettie, undated (Box 11)
      - Morris, Lizzie, 1976, undated (Box 11)
      - Mpazakis, Minnie, undated (Box 11)
      - Parrish, Hattie Bell, 1975, undated (Box 11)
      - Peaks, William S., 1976, undated (Box 11)
      - Rigsbee, Otis H., 1975-1980, undated (Box 11)
      - Riley, Howard L., 1975-1979, undated (Box 11)
      - Roberts, Nannie, 1975-1980, undated (Box 11)
      - Satterfield, Hattie, 1976, undated (Box 11)
      - Taylor, Mary Maggie, 1975-1980, undated (Box 11)
      - Terry, Lillian, 1976, undated (Box 12)
      - Tilley, John L., 1975-1982, undated (Box 12)
      - Tilley, Joyce, 1975-1981, undated (Box 12)
      - Tilley, Rutha Cordelia, 1976, undated (Box 12)
      - Turrentine, Mattie C., 1975, undated (Box 12)
      - Umstead, Emma Harris, 1975-1982, undated (Box 12)
      - Umstead, Sarah Vertee, 1976-1980, undated (Box 12)
      - Veasley, Nellie, 1976, undated (Box 12)
      - Wade, Allice Ramsey, 1975-1980, undated (Box 12)
      - Wilkins, Hattie, 1976-1980, undated (Box 12)
      - Williams, Bessie, undated (Box 12)
      - Williams, Elizabeth Hall, 1975-1981, undated (Box 12)
      - Wilson, Lola, 1975-1982 (Box 12)
      - Yancey, Leana, 1976, undated (Box 12)
    - Audiocassettes: Interviewees: (Box 13)
      Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead: Audiocassettes: Interviewees: Cross Reference List
      The following is a cross reference list of audiocassettes that contain interviews with more than one person. For example to listen to the interview with Aiken, retrieve the audiocassette listed under Garrett. To be sure all audiocassettes relating to a particular person have been retrieved, look at both lists.
      Restricted
      Aiken see Garrett
      Aiken, L. see Riley
      Ball see Chambers
      Ball, Polly see Mangum, Ella
      Ball, Polly see Tilley, Joyce
      Blalock, Sallie see Riley
      Blalock see Wilson
      Blalock see Garrett
      Dr. Brieger see Tilley
      Briggs, Nanny see Chambers, Walter
      Bullock (married) see Riley
      Bullock, Jonah see Satterfield, Hattie
      Chambers, Walter see McBride, Julie
      Chambers (married) see Riley
      Clayton, Ethel see Harris, Betty Lee
      Clayton see Wilson
      Clayton see Riley
      Crabtree see Riley
      Crabtree see McBride, Julie
      Daniel see Yancey
      Garrett, James see Satterfield, Hattie
      Harris, Myrtle see Tilley, Joyce
      Harris, Myrtle see Mangum, Ella
      Heron, Becky and Duncan see Jeffries, Lattie G.
      Hill, Betty see Satterfield, Hattie
      Hill see Chambers
      Hill see Harris, Betty Lee
      Ing see Yancey
      Ivy see Williams
      Jeffries, Lattie see Mangum, Ella
      Jeffries, M. see Tilley, Joyce
      Jeffries see Garrett
      Jordan, Hattie see Satterfield, Hattie
      Jordan see Harris, Betty Lee
      Lipscomb, Earlie see Terry, Lillian
      Littrell, Julie see Terry, Lillian
      Littrell see Riley
      Lunsford see Garrett
      Lunsford see Wilson
      Lyons, Maynard see McBride, Julie
      Lyons see Riley
      Mangum, Wade see Riley
      Mangum see Harris, Betty Lee
      McBride, Julie see Chambers, Wilcie
      McBride see Chambers
      McCrea, Viola see Ball, Annie
      McCrea see Garrett
      Morris see Briggs, Nannie
      Mpazakis see Williams
      Parrish, Hattie Bell see Satterfield, Hattie
      Rigsbee, Otis see Chambers, Walter
      Rigsbee see Ellis, Vesta
      Roberts, Nanny see Ball, Annie
      Roberts see Tilley
      Satterfield see Chambers
      Taylor, Mary see Terry, Lillian
      Taylor, Mary M. see Riley
      Thacker-Cancer see Riley and UNC students
      Tilley, John see McBride, Julie
      Tilley, Joyce see Ball, Annie
      Turrentine, Mattie see McBride, Julie
      Umstead, Emma see Chambers, Wilcie
      Umstead, Vertie (Epilogue) see Tilley
      Wilkins see Chambers
      Williams see Chambers and Wilson
      Wilson see Garrett
      Audiocassettes: Interviewees: (The number 2 after several names indicates there are 2 audiocassettes containing that person's interview.)
      - Aiken, Luetta (Box 13)
      - Ball, Annie (2) (Box 13)
      - Ball, Polly (Box 13)
      - Blalock, Lizzie (Box 13)
      - Blalock, Sallie (Box 13)
      - Briggs, Nannie (2) (Box 13)
      - Bullock, Jonah (Box 13)
      - Chambers, Walter (2) (Box 13)
      - Chambers, Wilcie (2) (Box 13)
      - Chambers (2) (Box 13)
      - Clayton, Ethel (Box 13)
      - Clayton, Vera Elma (Box 13)
      - Crabtree, Ernest (Box 13)
      - Ellis, Vesta (Box 13)
      - Farlow, Ora, 1975, undated (Box 13)
      - Garrett, James M. (Box 13)
      - Garrett (Box 13)
      - Harris, Betty Lee (2) (Box 13)
      - Harris, Myrtle (Box 13)
      - Hill, Betty (Box 13)
      - Jeffries, Lattie G. (2) (Box 13)
      - Jeffries (Box 13)
      - Jordan, Hattie R. (Box 13)
      - Lipscomb, Earlie (2) (Box 14)
      - Littrell, Julie (Box 14)
      - Lunsford, Elsie R. (Box 14)
      - Lyons, Maynard (Box 14)
      - McBride, Julie (2) (Box 14)
      - McCrea, Viola (Box 14)
      - Mangum, Ella (2) (Box 14)
      - Moore, Quinettie (2) (Box 14)
      - Morris, Lizzie (Box 14)
      - Parrish, Hattie Bell (Box 14)
      - Peaks, William S. (Box 14)
      - Rigsbee, Otis H. (2) (Box 14)
      - Riley, Howard L. (2) (Box 14)
      - Riley (2) (Box 14)
      - Riley and UNC students (Box 14)
      - Roberts, Nanny (Box 14)
      - Satterfield, Hattie (2) (Box 14)
      - Taylor, Mary Maggie (2) (Box 14)
      - Terry, Lillian (2) (Box 14)
      - Tilley, John L. (Box 14)
      - Tilley, Joyce (2) (Box 15)
      - Tilley, Rutha Cordelia (Mrs. D. B.) (Box 15)
      - Tilley (Box 15)
      - Turrentine, Mattie C. (Box 15)
      - Umstead, Emma (Box 15)
      - Umstead, Sarah Vertee (Box 15)
      - Veasley (Box 15)
      - Wade, Allice Ramsey (Box 15)
      - Wilkins, Hattie (Box 15)
      - Williams, Elizabeth Hall (Box 15)
      - Williams (Box 15)
      - Wilson, Lola (Box 15)
      - Wilson (Box 15)
      - Yancey (Box 15)
  - Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead: (Box 16)
    - Negatives,1981 (Box 16)
    - Oral History Day, Duke University, 1984, June 9 (Box 16)
    - Photo essay,1985 (Box 16)
    - Pictures:
      - Churches, undated (Box 16)
      - Grandmother Caring for Children, undated (Box 16)
      - Interviewees:, (3 folders)
        - Ball, Annie (Box 16)
        - Ball, Polly (Box 16)
        - Blalock, Lizzie (Box 16)
        - Blalock, Sally (Box 16)
        - Briggs, Nannie Mae (Box 16)
        - Bullock, Jonah (Box 16)
        - Chambers, Walter H. (Box 16)
        - Chambers, Wilcie (Box 16)
        - Crabtree, Ernest (Box 16)
        - Daniel, Mabel (Box 16)
        - Ellis, Vesta (Box 16)
        - Garrett, James Maynard (Box 16)
        - Harris, Betty Lee (Box 16)
        - Jeffries, Lattie (Box 16)
        - Jordan, Hattie Riley (Box 16)
        - Lipscomb, Earlie Nathan (Box 16)
        - Lyons, Maynard (Box 16)
        - Mangum, Ella Lyons (Box 16)
        - McCrae, Viola (Box 16)
        - Rigsbee, Otis (Box 16)
        - Riley, Howard (Box 17)
        - Satterfield, Hattie (Box 17)
        - Taylor, Mary Maggie (Box 17)
        - Tilley, John (Box 17)
        - Tilley, Joyce (Box 17)
        - Umstead, Emma H. (Box 17)
        - Umstead, Vertee (Box 17)
        - Wilkins, Hattie (Box 17)
        - Woods, Sally (Box 17)
      - Stores in Area, undated (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1979-1981, undated (Box 17)
    - Reviews,1989 (Box 17)
    - Reviews and correspondence, 1981-1987, undated, (2 folders) (Box 17)
    - Slides,1981 (Box 17)
    - Videocassette:
      - 1988 (Box 17)
      - Preparation, 1985-1990 (Box 17)
  - Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead: Oversize Photographs (Box 17a)
    - Pictures:
      - Beauty Hiding Poverty, undated (Box 17a)
      - Churches,1979, undated (Box 17a)
      - Coffee shop,1979, undated (Box 17a)
      - Interviewees:
        - Blalock, Sally, undated (Box 17a)
        - Briggs, Nannie Mae, undated (Box 17a)
        - Clayton, Ethel, undated (Box 17a)
        - Clayton, Mrs. J., undated (Box 17a)
        - Ellis, Vesta, undated (Box 17a)
        - Lipscomb, Earlie, undated (Box 17a)
        - Mangum, Ella Lyons, undated (Box 17a)
        - Satterfield, Hattie, undated (Box 17a)
        - Taylor, Mary Maggie, 1979 (Box 17a)
        - Wade, Alice Ramsey, 1979 (Box 17a)
        - Unidentified man, undated (Box 17a)
  - Don't Send Me Flowers When I'm Dead: (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous, 1973-1983, Apr., undated, (3 folders) (Box 18)
  - Facts about Smoking and Health, 1964-1977 (Box 18)
  - Health Status and Health Care Under Apartheid Rule in South Africa (Lecture):
    - Background material, 1957-1984, undated (Box 18)
    - Clippings, 1985-1987, undated (Box 18)
  - The Mind is not the Heart:
    - Correspondence, 1985-1990, undated, (2 folders) (Box 18)
    - Correspondence: Publication rejections, 1987-1988 (Box 19)
    - Duke University Press, 1987-1989, undated (Box 19)
    - Pictures:
      - Boston, undated (Box 19)
      - Epilogue, undated (Box 19)
      - North Carolina, undated (Box 19)
      - South Africa, 1967, undated (Box 19)
    - Reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous,1989 (Box 19)
  - Studies in South African Infant Growth, M.D. thesis,1955, (1 vol.) (Box 19)
  - Where were you in World War II? (Lecture),1989 (Box 19)
  - Miscellaneous: (Box 20)
    - Book reviews, 1977-1990 (Box 20)
    - Creative Writing Class, Harvard, 1967-1969 (Box 20)
    - Duke University Campus Club Lecture Series,1984 (Box 20)
    - Health facilitators, 1970-1981 (Box 20)
    - Primary care and consumer participation, 1973-1978 (Box 20)
    - 1981-1983, undated (Box 20)
  - Others:
    - Offenberger, Claude: Educational Implications in the Governance of a Health Center, 1969-1989, (2 folders) (Box 20)
    - Poverty and racism, 1968-1970 (Box 20)
- Martha M. Eliot Family Health Center, 1967-1990, undated
  Correspondence, clippings, photographs and organizational records in the form of reports, meeting minutes, newsletters, agendas, charts, and a scrapbook. Explanatory notes added later by Salber.
  Arranged chronologically and then alphabetically.
  - 1976-1986, undated (Box 20)
  - Advisory Committee to the Director, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
  - Clippings, 1970-1972 (Box 21)
  - Dedication Day:
    - 1968 (Box 21)
    - Pictures,1968 (Box 21)
  - Grants, 1968-1970 (Box 21)
  - Health Advisory Committee, 1967-1969, (3 folders) (Box 21)
  - History,1967 (Box 21)
  - Letters of farewell, poetry, and miscellaneous, 1967-1970 (Box 21)
  - Medical teams,1968 (Box 21)
  - Nursing program, 1968-1989, undated (Box 21)
  - Policy meetings, 1967-1989, undated, (2 folders) (Box 22)
  - Reports, 1968-1971, (3 folders) (Box 22)
  - Social Service Department, 1967-1970 (Box 22)
  - Staff meetings, 1967-1970, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Training Course I and II, 1967-1969, (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous:
    - 1968-1989, undated (Box 23)
    - Salber's notes on pertinent meetings,1969 (Box 23)
- Duke University Medical Center, 1965-1990, undated